[Music] Look what they sent me from the pig uncle journalists or informants
gorrino tío periodistas o informadores
both because they are there at the bottom of the
ambos porque están ahí al pie de la
news and that he was very offended now
noticia y que se ofendió mucho ahora
because they were criticizing him because I do
porque le estuvieron criticando porque
n't know if it has reached you in Mexico but there
no sé si os ha llegado a México pero
was a disaster in Valencia here in
hubo un desastre en Valencia aquí en
Spain you want to browse the
España quieres Navegar de forma segura
internet safely and also access all the
en internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix hbo Max or Disney Plus
como Netflix hbo Max o Disney Plus
cyberg VPN And I don't know if you know
cyberg VPN Y es que no sé si lo sabes
but there is content that is not available in your country
pero hay contenidos que en tu país no
and with this little trick
están disponibles y con este truquillo
you can access all the content wherever you
puedes acceder a todo el contenido est
are I don't know if you know what
es donde estés no sé si sabes lo que es
a VPN is but it is an extension that you
una VPN pero es una extensión que le
put on your internet with which it masks
pones a tu internet con la que enmascara
the IP and apart from browsing completely
la IP y aparte de Navegar completamente
safely and anonymously without
seguro y anónimo sin que nadie pueda
anyone being able to know who you are and where you are It helps you access some content that is blocked in your country there are movies and series on your favorite platforms that are not available there are television programs for example on
programas de televisión por ejemplo en
media set content that if you try to
media set contenidos que si los intentas
watch them outside of Spain they have a geoblock
ver fuera de España tienen un geobloqueo
that does not allow you Well with cyberghost
que no te lo permite Pues con cyberghost
VPN that is over Apart  of being
VPN eso se acabó Aparte de estar
protected browsing anonymously you
protegido navegando bajo el anonimato
will be able to access content from all over
podrás acceder a los contenido de todo
the planet in addition you will have
el planeta además tendrás privacidad
Total privacy since it keeps your connection
Total ya que mantiene tu conexión en
private and protects your data
privado y protege tus datos velocidad
ultra fast speed to eliminate the lake in
ultr rápida para el eliminar el lago en
any online game with which you
cualquier juego online con los que
can enjoy live broadcasts without
podrás disfrutar de directos sin
interruptions and as I have already told you
interrupciones y como ya os he dicho
Freedom to access all the
Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of 83%
quieras además aprovecha son 83 de
off using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and watch out
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try cyberg VPN 45
ojo porque puedes probar cyberg VPN 45
days without obligation and if you are not convinced you
días sin compromiso y si no te convence
ask for a refund and you will get it back
pides el reembolso y te devuelve la pasa
so don't wait any longer to protect your
así que no esperes más para proteger tu
connection and increase your
conexión y aumentar tu experiencia en
internet experience run Click on the link in the
internet corre Le Click al enlace de la
description and take advantage of this super
descripción y aprovecha esta super
cyberg VPN offer to browse
oferta cyberg VPN para navegar
completely free and safe with the issue
completamente libre y seguro con el tema
of dan to a storm and others where it
del dan a una tormenta y demás donde se
flooded many people lost businesses there have
inundó mucha gente perdió negocios ha
been deaths I know what and well
habido muertos sabido no sé qué y bueno
and he says he doesn't know what he's complaining about that
y él dice que no sabe de qué se queja
he went to do his job to
que él ha ido a hacer su trabajo a
report he drove there that he said it
informar condujo hasta allí que dijo que
took 24 hours to travel six on the
tardó 24 horas en recorrer seis en
road I don't know how he did it to
carretera yo no sé cómo lo ha hecho para
take 24 hours to  six I don't know where you
tardar 24 horas en seis esto no sé dónde
got this from what does sound familiar is that
lo saca lo que lo que sí me suena es que
I was able to say that I was out for 24 hours
yo he podido decir que estuve 24 horas
because I left home at around 2
fuera porque salí de casa como a las 2
in the morning and I came back home at 1 or
de la mañana y volví a casa a la 1 más o
so. I left home at 2 in the
menos en yo salí de casa a las 2 de la
morning I got there in the morning and
mañana llegué allí por la mañana además
I also chatted on the phone for a while
estuve Charlando por teléfono un rato
with Tesa and for a while with Alanne and then it
con tesa y otro rato con alanne y ahí me
occurred to me that I spent the 6 hours on the road and I
dio que eché las 6 s horas de C camino y
arrived in the morning I looked for a place
llegué por la mañana busqué un sitio
to sleep or whatever but it was
para dormir algun o lo que sea pero era
impossible okay I looked for a place to
imposible vale busqué un sitio para
sleep in the car now with the
dormirme en el coche ya con la luz del
sunlight I don't know I don't know how much impossible
Sol no sé que no sé cuánto imposible
I met up with a follower I think it was
quedé con una seguidora en creo que era
Alfafar it could have been Alfafar I think it
alfafar puede ser que fuera alfafar Creo
was Alfafar and we recorded in the morning
que fue alfafar e grabamos por la mañana
that part of the report that we did
aquella parte del reportaje que hicimos
okay em that was the part where
vale em que fue la parte en la que
you saw that the follower guided me around
visteis que la seguidora me Me guía por
the town and showed me everything and then I
el pueblo y me enseña todo y luego me
stopped to eat uh I ate at a Burger Well
paré a comer eh comí en un Burger Bueno
in fact I also saw something I think at
de hecho también vi algo creo que al
noon the this part of the of
mediodía la la parte esta de la de de
the  science no this structure that I had
las cienci no la estructura esta que no
never seen before I started to see it I had not been
la había visto nunca me puse a verla no
I think I had never been
había estado Creo que nunca había estado
to Valencia or if I had been in Valencia until
en Valencia o si estado en Valencia hasa
By the way I gave pily the surprise and from
De paso le di la sorpresa a pily y de
there I ran that I had
ahí ya me fui corriendo que había
met up with Rubén after lunch at
quedado con Rubén después de comer a las
3 or around there and then we were there for three or
3 o por ahí y y ya pues estuvimos tres o
four hours that Rubén made the route for me
cuatro horas que me que me hizo la ruta
wonderful Rubén gier who I know
Rubén maravilloso Rubén gier que yo sé
that a lot of people like him or dislike him there are
que a mucha gente le cae bien o mal hay
a lot of people but he was great with me
mucha gente pero conmigo se portó genial
thanks to him we were able to have that report
gracias a él pudimos tener ese reportaje
and I will always remember him you
y yo siempre se lo voy a recordar lás
did an enormous job in the Dana in fact
hiz una labor enorme en la Dana de hecho
Rubén told me when we got back already or At
Rubén me dijo ya cuando volvimos ya ó A
6 in the afternoon or something like that TR 3 hours I was
las 6 de la tarde o cosa así TR 3 horas
3 3 and a half hours recording 6 6 and
estuv 3 3 horas y media grabando 6 6 y
a bit I told me to stay because I was
pico yo me dijo de quear porque yo
thinking of buying whatever clothes
pensaba comprarme lo que sea de ropa por
there anywhere and looking for a
ahí en cualquier sitio y buscarme un
hotel to sleep for the night and
hotel para dormir para echar la noche y
when I saw it was 6 in the afternoon 6:30 it
yo cuando vi eran las 6 de la tarde 6:30
seemed like I got the car at 12 to
dio cómo yo comoo el coche a las 12 a la
1 I'm sleeping in my bed not in a
1 estoy yo durmiendo en mi cama no en un
hotel anymore and besides, it doesn't bother me, I
hotel ya me demás que a mí no me pesa yo
put on a podcast or I start talking
me pongo un podcast o me pongo a hablar
on the phone or whatever, I don't
por teléfono o lo que sea a mí no me
mind the car smoke and I and I left and that's why I
pesa el coche fum y me y me fui y por
think I mentioned on
eso fue que creo que yo mencioné en
one occasion that I was out for 24 hours, of
alguna ocasión que estuve 24 horas fuera
course, I was out for 24 hours, I left at 12 gosh
claro estuve 24 horas salí a las 12 gorr
when are you going to do a job like that, you
tú cuándo vas a hacer un trabajo así
know what you do, you pig when you
sabes lo que haces tú gorrino cuando tú
go on a trip with the family you act all
te vas de viaje con la familia te pones
geeky like it's a
de friky a ser como si fuera un viaje
tourist trip for YouTubers in Barcelona
turístico de los youtubers por Barcelona
you went and you were surrounding everything
te fuiste y estuviste rodeando todo lo
that had to do with me and Dallas
que tuviera que ver conmigo y con Dallas
eh you took pictures in Santa Susana with
eh te hiciste fotos en Santa Susana con
the sign and then you went to Andorra and
el cartel y luego te fuiste a andorra y
you acted like it was
te pusiste como como si fuera aquello
Disneyland contacting several you
Disneylandia contactando a varios que
contacted some YouTubers that I'm not
contactaste a algunos youtubers que no
going to say their names out of respect okay
voy a decir los nombres por respeto vale
but they didn't stay with you that nothing
pero que no quedaron contigo que nada
more than that stayed with you I think the delos
más que quedo contigo Creo que el delos
and the encouragement but you called others you
y el animo pero llamaste a otros más
called others  what did I tell you what the [ __ ]
llamaste a otros más que te di qué [__]
pamona I don't know this guy You're welcome what the
pamona este no lo conozco De nada qué
[ __ ] is this guy talking to me about meeting him he
[__] me está hablando este de queda con
started calling several youtubers I
é se puso a llamar a varios youtubers o
mean do a job Well what the [ __ ] are you going to
sea haz un trabajito Bueno qué [__] vas
work if you had this thing
a trabajar si tuviste el tema este de de
with Marif Fery and you weren't even able to
lo de marif fery y no fuiste capaz ni
make more than one video and then he was there for
hac más de un vídeo y luego estuvo allí
three hours of recording to show
tres horas de grabación para enseñar
that and come back and a lot of people
aquello y volverse y mucha gente le ha
are criticizing him because he even put on the boots
está criticando porque hasta las botas
that ended up covered in mud he
que se puso y que acabaron en barro las
ended up throwing them in a trash can when
acabó tirando en una papelera cuando
there were people there who didn't even have shoes
había gente allí que no tiene ni calzado
to put them on lie okay I mean I
para poder ponerse mentira vale o sea yo
told Rubén what do I do with the boots
le dije a Rubén Qué hago con las botas
because obviously the BMW wasn't
porque evidentemente las botas no las
going to put them on Not for nothing but
iba a montar el bmv No por nada sino
because I have a nice car well and they
porque tengo un coche bonito bueno y y
are boots that had been walking through
son botas que habían estado andando por
all the [ __ ] and that isn't mud if it
toda la [__] y eso no es barro si
were mud if it were a little mud Well that
fuera barro si fuera un poco barro Bueno
's what there is like when I go to the
pues es lo que hay como cuando voy a la
beach It's that the [ __ ] of the garages
playa Es que la [__] de los garajes
where we got into okay that what happened with
donde nos metimos vale eso lo de lo de
Dana wasn't mud It was mud mixed
la Dana no era fango Era fango mezclado
with gasoline with corpses with
con gasolina con cadáveres con aguas
sewage or whatever  as you will understand in my
fecales o sea como tú comprenderás en mi
car I do not ride those boots that's what
coche no monto esas botas para eso
boots are for to put them on and
sirven las botas para ponértelas y
when you go to get in the car
cuando te vayas a montar en el coche las
throw them in one in a trash can and get
tiras en una en una basurita y te montas
in your car with those that no I am not going to
en tu coche con los que no no voy a
drive with With the rain boot in
conducir con Con la bota de agua de
fact I told them do you want them to
hecho yo les dije las queréis ustedes
hit them with a hose and will it work for you and they
pegarle un manguerazo y os sirve y me
told me No man, that's not how we are either
dijeron No hombre así no estamos tampoco
and and out okay clown you're stupid
y y fuera vale payaso que eres tonto
When are you going to do a job for yourself to
Cuándo vas a hacerte un trabajo para tú
criticize in a pass see if you get it right
criticar en un pasa a ver si te enteras
now once and for all for you to criticize
ya de una [__] vez para tú criticar
Do it yourself better stop harassing it's the
Hazlo tú mejor deja de acosar que es el
only job you know how to do harass that you
único trabajo que sabes hacer acosar que
're preparing a video now about Mau
estás preparando ahora un vídeo de Mau
RG that you're not even informing yourself you're
RG que no estás ni informándote estás
pending as you already know that your video is going to be about
pendiente como ya sabes que tu vídeo va
defending Al Dolores whatever
a tratar de defender a al dolores lo que
you find negative about Ale Dolores you're not
te encuentres negativo de Ale dolores no
going to put it you're only going to
lo vas a poner solamente te vas a
find what benefits her you're only
encontrar lo que le beneficie solamente
going to put what benefits you for you to
vas a poner lo que te beneficie para tú
criticize me because I do a
criticarme a mí porque yo haga un
report that you're a Shameless
reportaje que eres un Sinvergüenza
because on top of that and on top of that a thing dude that
porque encima e encima una cosa tío que
that no You think I've
que que no Tú te crees que yo le he
made money from that that maybe I
sacado dinero a eso que a lo mejor me
spent on gas how much could I have
gasté en gasolina cuánto me he podido
spent on gas family 1000000 €
gastar en gasolina familia 1000000 €
How much does the video have 880,000 views I
Cuánto tiene el vídeo 880,000 visitas
think it has Maybe I have generated
creo que tiene A lo mejor he generado
400 with that video Do you think it's worth it to me to
400 con ese vídeo Tú te crees que a mí
spend 24 hours on the
me merece la pena pegarme 24 horas en la
street spending money on gas to
calle gastarme el dinero en gasolina en
eat eh the clothes that I bought that day
comer eh la ropa que me compré ese día
for the chore the Editors Do you
para para la faen los Editores Tú te
think I've made money from that
crees que yo le he sacado dinero a eso
more than sitting here with the can of
más que está aquí sentado con la lata de
mte like you and making gossip I didn't do it
mte como tú y y hacer salseo no lo hice
from the heart I did it to do something
de corazón lo hice para hac una cosa
different and to give it visibility which
diferente y para darle visibilidad que
was what my followers in
fue lo que me pidieron mis seguidores de
Valencia asked me for when you do something good don't
valencia tú cuando hagas una cosa buena
harass criticize dude you don't
que no sea acosar critica tío que no
do [ __ ] [ __ ] and nothing else you
haces una [__] [__] y nada más que
know how to criticize when you don't do anything you're
sabes criticar cuando tú no haces nada
worthless dude a
que no vales para nada tío que un
little more of a youtuber because d I would
poquito más de youtuber porque d la
leave the controversies that arise even
dejaba las polémicas que se pone hasta
that well dude regardless  of this
eso tío bueno independientemente de esto
then he says why do they criticize him for
luego dice que por qué lo critican por
doing his job and going to inform but
hacer su trabajo e ir a informar pero
of course what are the sensationalists going to understand
claro qué van a entender los
if the only thing they look for is
amarillistas si lo único que buscan es
socialism and selling themselves as victims
el scial ismo y el venderse de víctimas
and directly selling the drama you
y el vender directamente el drama tú
are stupid selling it is that you are an
eres tonto vender el es que eres
[ __ ] according to what happens is that you are an
[__] según pasa es que eres
[ __ ] by the mother who gave birth to me man
[__] por la madre que me parió tío
with the [ __ ] [ __ ] of harassing man with the
con la [__] [__] de acosar tío con la
[ __ ] [ __ ] of harassing selling the drama and
[__] [__] de acosar vender el drama y
playing the victim go to Dana to give
hacerse la víctima ir a la Dana a dar
visibility with the people who
visibilidad con la de gente que
contributed things, who donated things for my
aportaron cosas que donaron cosas por mi
[ __ ] video man they are repulsive man they are
[__] vídeo tío son repulsivos tío son
repulsive what are they going to understand what
repulsivos qué van a entender ellos de
criticism is in itself do you understand
lo que es una crítica en sí entiendes tú
criticism that you have a lot of coherence
de crítica que tienes mucha coherencia
criticizing You really are a bad
criticando De verdad eres una mala
person and your community is a
persona y tu comunidad es una comunidad
toxic community and I hate what they think
tóxica y me sabe a culo lo que piensen
about me it tastes like ass that is 50 years old
sobre mí sabe a culo que tiene 50 años
what the [ __ ] are you talking about elestra stop
qué [__] estás hablando elestra deja de
whitewashing criminal and stop defaming
blanquear delincuente y deja de difamar
that they will throw your account again it tastes like
que te van a volver a tirar la cuenta me
ass Well to me it tastes like piss what
sabe culo Pues a mí me sabe a pis lo que
you tell me  idiot keep crying keep
me digas tú idiota sigan llorando sigan
burning has done a lot egun motivated me to
ardir ha hecho mucho egun me motivo
exercise flexed biceps Yeah yeah that thing
hacer ejercicio bíceps flexionado Sí sí
about putting your foot in the mud
que que lo de meter el pie en el fango
reminds you of something else I'm not going to shut up I'm
le recuerda otra cosa no me voy a callar
going to upload to raide to laser to egun to
voy a subir a raide a láser a egun a
mexiverga to Nitro Launcher to serene to
mexiverga a Nitro Launcher a serene a
peluca to whoever I want here
peluca a todo el que me dé aquí mi gana
because that is called freedom of
porque eso se llama libertad de
expression sir yes yes yes yes yes yes yes s
expresión señor sí sí sí sí sí sí sí s
nothing more than you nothing more that you need to
nada más que te nada más que te falta
upload to it Gameplay you
subir a it Gameplay a ese también lo
can upload that one too if you want yes yes
puedes subir también si quieres sí sí
mother of God the gang to mention
madre de Dios la cuadrilla que mencionar
in a ply pla Eh Just like you have it I
en un pli plá Eh Así como tú la tienes
have it too and we all have it
Yo también la tengo y todos la tenemos
so find another job friend you'll
así que busca otro oficio amigo que
look ridiculous I won't be left
quedas en ridículo no me van a quedar
honey honey stop stop stop because here I have
cariño cariño frena frena frena que aquí
something else to see of this [ __ ]
tengo algo más que ver de esta [__]
[ __ ] Lili because here the one who just
[__] Lili que aquí la que acaba de
said that the raes weren't
decir que que lo de raes no eran
threats is you eh So stop
amenazas eres tú eh Así que déjate de de
making a fool of yourself I don't believe it I don't believe it I don't
harla de ridículo no me lo creo no me lo
believe it I don't believe it the
creo no me lo creo no me lo creo el
process of a production company  eh from
proceso de una productora eh de
television in this country that is
televisión de este país que está
accused eh For removing
imputada eh Por sacar documentación
legal and sensitive documentation, she has not said accused
legal y sensible no ha dicho imputado
in front of RAED no no no she has not said
delante de raed no no no no ha dicho
accused in front of RAE of the people
imputado delante de RAE de las personas
and she is accused of three crimes eh
y está imputada por tres delitos eh
crime against the administration and she remains
delito contra la administración y se
silent but yes But what happens but if
calla pero si Pero qué pasa pero si
accused was not us clarify you do not
imputado no era nos aclaris no os ponéis
agree not even yourselves no no you do not
de acuerdo ni ustedes mismos no no no os
agree yourselves
ponéis de acuerdo ustedes mismos
then accused okay accused It's not worth it
entonces imputado vale imputado No vale
I'm talking to see if yes I have
estoy hablando a ver sí eso sí lo he
seen that he says that if I have seen what Ray
visto dice que si he visto lo de Ray
said that I get involved Perico Yes yes I have seen it yes I have
diciendo que me meto Perico Sí sí lo he
seen it I have seen it I have
visto sí lo he visto lo he visto lo he
seen man I am going to react to this part
visto tío voy a reaccionar a esta parte
of the chat the other day because this
de la tertua del otro día porque este
salce passed me by nothing grandpa that you have to
salce se me pasó nada abuelo que te toca
change professions because the
cambiar de profesión porque la señora
least hypocritical and faceless lady
menos hipócrita y cara de tabla te lo
orders you to XD me but hypocritical no the
ordena XD yo pero hipócrita no los
following are eh be it is that they are worthless
siguientes son eh sea es que no valen
eh They are absolutely worthless
para nada eh No valen absolutamente para
what they say eh eh Electra I do not
nada lo que digan eh eh Electra No te
understand you if this community You give a
entiendo si esta comunidad Te importa un
damn about what they say about  you why did you
culo por lo que dicen de ti por qué te
spend two weeks crying like a
pegaste dos semanas llorando como la
little brat about the things they write here in
niñata de las cosas que escriben acá en
the chat someone send our
el chat que alguien le mande a nuestro
Trojan Horse Electra our dear
Caballo de Troya Electra nuestra querida
Loli Hey but man the crossovers They are
Loli Oye pero tío los crossovers Son
incredible I mean the crossovers are the
increíbles o sea los crossovers son la
best eh trust you the crossover that gets
[__] eh fíate tú el crossover que se
together there man a crazy lady
junta ahí tío una loca de la señoreros
crazy man who was a friend of Dallas and now
loco que era amigo de Dallas y ahora se
a lady comes and now she passes him and
viene una señora y ahora le un pasa y
now man literal association of bad guys
ahora tío asociación literal de malitos
Why Well because it's very simple em
Por qué Pues porque es muy sencillo em
because they are people who have done things that
porque son gente que han hecho cosas que
objectively nobody is going to agree with them
objetivamente nadie les va a dar la
okay But this is like the other
razón vale Pero esto es como la la otra
lady and the other lady and all of you
señora y la otra señora y todos los que
already know okay Peppa Antonia the
ya sabéis vale la Peppa la Antonia la
other one and the guy on the motorcycle and all of them
otra y el de la moto y todos ellos
objectively nobody is going to agree with them
objetivamente nadie les va a dar la
This is not like for example when
razón Esto no es como por ejemplo cuando
I argue with a stutter that by the way
yo discuto con tartaja que por cierto
we are buddies no teas there no or what happens that
estamos compá no teas allá no o qué pasa
some will agree with him others They
que unos le darán la razón a él otros Me
will agree with me no no no no no These
darán la razón a mí no no no no no Estos
are people who have done things that
son gente que han hecho cosas que
objectively everyone Nobody agrees with them
objetivamente todo el mundo Nadie les da
what  that's what they do that
la la razón qué es lo que hacen que
between them they make this association so
entre ellos hacen esta asociación para
you agree with me and you tell me
tú me das la razón a mí y me dices que
yes yes yes yes yes guana yes guana and I agree with
sí sí sí sí guana sí guana y yo te doy
you there's RAED criticizing
la razón a ti está el raed criticando a
Dallas about the token and he left
Dallas con lo del token y se ha ido hasa
late for Peppa's live and that's it and
tarde al directo de la Peppa y ya está y
Peppa is criticizing me about
está la Peppa criticándome a mí con lo
the 10,500 and she has RA on her
de los 10,500 y tiene al ra en su
live it doesn't make sense do you understand and
directo no tiene sentido me entiendes y
so on with all of them and so on with each and every one
así con todos y así con todos y cada uno
of them each and every one of them do you
de ellos todos y cada uno de ellos me
understand why Because Well yes yes I'm going along with
entiendes por qué Porque Bueno sí sí yo
you yes yes RAE you are the
te sigo el rollo a ti sí sí RAE tú eres
victim Yes yes RAE they are
la víctima Sí sí RAE te están
slandering you Yes yes RAE and you go along with
calumniando Sí sí RAE y tú me sigues el
me yes yes it's true Pepa the 240 you
rollo a mí sí sí es verdad [__] los 240
did very well perfect and that's it
lo hiciste muy bien perfecto y es así ya
and there's nothing else to talk about they are
está y no ha más nada que hablar son
frustrated and they
frustrados y se
[Music]
[Música]
join together and
unen y